animated-teeth.com 2019-05-18

# Privacy Statement for Animated-Teeth.com and its owner WMDS, Inc.

WMDS, Inc. is the sole owner web site Animated-Teeth.com and any and all information collected by this web site.

## Web site information collection and use.

The following paragraphs describe different ways by which information may be collected from a visitor to Animated-Teeth.com. Following each description there is an explanation of how this information is or might be utilized by WMDS, Inc. or other parties we have partnered with.

### a) Information collected via our Dental eCard service.

A site visitor may, at their discretion, choose to take advantage of our Dental eCard service. This service requires the user to submit a recipient email address. Optionally, the user may also enter their name, the recipient's name and a message.

This information is retained in our database temporarily, solely for purpose of performing the eCard service (sending the eCard). This information is not otherwise evaluated, aggregated, distributed or used in any way.

### b) Information collected via email correspondence.

From time to time, persons may choose to send unsolicited email to our site. Each letter is read, and depending on the nature of its contents, an email response may returned. While a copy of each letter is documented by printing it out and placing it in our files, none of the information found in the letter, including the sender's email address and identity, is retained by WMDS, Inc. for any other purposes, or shared with anyone outside of WMDS, Inc.

Site visitors may at their choosing send to Animated-Teeth.com pictures showing their smile and teeth. At our discretion we may choose to edit these images as a way of demonstrating the types of cosmetic changes a dentist might possibly make. All images submitted become the property of WMDS, Inc. who has the right to reproduce, modify, and publish the image. The information found in the email letter itself, including the sender's email address and identity, is printed out for our files but is not otherwise retained or utilized by WMDS, Inc. for any purposes, or shared with anyone outside of WMDS, Inc.

### c) Information collected in Animated-Teeth.com's log files.

Our web server's operating system creates log files documenting the information requested from our web site server by Animated-Teeth.com's visitors. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp. We may choose to analyze this log information so to evaluate the movements of our site's users, site usage trends, and to gather broad demographic information about visitors to our site. IP addresses, etc... are not linked to personally identifiable information. We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers, but this information is not linked to any personally identifiable data.

### d) Cookies and other tracking methods.

##### Why do we have a cookie notification on our website?

Like many other websites, Animated-Teeth.com utilizes browser cookies (small text files placed on a website visitor's device (computer, smartphone, etc...), documenting activity that took place during their visit.)

We use cookies or similar tracking methods to analyze our traffic, provide social media features and personalize website content and ads. They are also used to share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners.

##### So why the notice?

European Union laws require that publishers give website visitors information about their use of cookies. Even though only a portion of our website traffic comes from Europe, we've placed the notice you've seen so to comply with these laws.

##### What type of information is collected?

The type of information that cookies document can include factors such as your IP address, ISP, the date of your last visits, your browser or whether you have Flash installed or JavaScript enabled.

##### Opting out.

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off cookies in the settings section of the web browser you are using, or by managing your web preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, doing so may affect how you are able to interact with our site.

Site visitors may explore their options for opting out of the use of cookies by our website advertisers by visiting the links below. Also, for information about how third parties we have partnered with might utilize cookies and other tracking methods when you visit our site, or leave our site and visit theirs, please select from the links below.

Privacy Policies of Animated-Teeth.com's partners:

  * Other Animated-Teeth.com links and advertising sponsors. \- Please contact us and we will help you obtain the information you require. 

### Third-Party Advertising

Some of the ads appearing on Animated-Teeth.com are delivered to users via a third-party advertising partner (currently Media.net and Google's Adsense program). Information about the privacy policies of these services and the companies for which they provide advertising can be found by using the links above.

### Links found in Animated-Teeth.com.

The content and advertising found on Animated-Teeth.com does contain links to other web sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these sites. We have been promised by our advertisers that any information collected in association with the initial presence of a pop-up window is only general in nature and is not linked to a visitor's personally identifiable information. We encourage our users to remain cognizant of when Animated-Teeth.com links direct them to other web sites. We also encourage users to read the privacy statements of each and every web site they visit. The privacy statement you are currently reading applies solely to information collected by Animated-Teeth.com.

### Legal Disclaimer.

Although we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our web site.

### Notification of changes.

If we decide to change our privacy policy we will post those changes in this privacy statement. We will only use information we have obtained in accordance with the privacy policy which was in force at that time when the information was collected.

### Contact information.

If users of Animated-Teeth.com have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, they should contact us at:

##### Postal address:

> WMDS, Inc.  
> 5126 Starboard Side Drive  
> Saint Louis, MO 63128  
> (314) 768-0156  
> 

Contact policy.

##### Email contact:

> This link will direct you to our general contact email address.

(May 24, 2018)
